<resources>
    <string name="app_name">IntegBDM</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_modtec_website">ModtecWebsite</string>

    <string-array name="clamp">
        <item>No Clamp</item>
        <item>Split clamp - Silver</item>
        <item>Split clamp - White</item>
        <item>Split clamp - Black</item>
        <item>Grommet clamp - Silver</item>
        <item>Grommet clamp - White</item>
        <item>Grommet clamp - Black</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="pole">
        <item>No Pole</item>
        <item>Ar-ray - Silver</item>
        <item>Ar-ray - White</item>
        <item>Ar-ray - Black</item>
        <item>Apollo4 - Silver</item>
        <item>Apollo4 - White</item>
        <item>Apollo4 - Black</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="arms">
        <item>No Arm</item>
        <item>Ar-ray Single - Silver</item>
        <item>Ar-ray Single - White</item>
        <item>Ar-ray Single - Black</item>
        <item>Ar-ray Dual - Silver</item>
        <item>Ar-ray Dual - White</item>
        <item>Ar-ray Dual - Black</item>
        <item>Apollo Single - Silver</item>
        <item>Apollo Single - White</item>
        <item>Apollo Single - Black</item>
        <item>Apollo Dual - Silver</item>
        <item>Apollo Dual - White</item>
        <item>Apollo Dual - Black</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="accessories">
        <item>No accessories</item>
        <item>Blade (Apollo only) - Silver</item>
        <item>Blade (Apollo only) - White</item>
        <item>Blade (Apollo only) - Black</item>
        <item>Blade Dual (Apollo only) - Silver</item>
        <item>Blade Dual (Apollo only) - White</item>
        <item>Blade Dual (Apollo only) - Black</item>
        <item>Traemate - Silver</item>
        <item>Traemate - White</item>
        <item>Traemate - Black</item>
        <item>Tabmate - Silver</item>
        <item>Tabmate - White</item>
        <item>Tabmate - Black</item>
        <item>Blade + Traemate (Apollo only) - Silver</item>
        <item>Blade + Traemate (Apollo only) - White</item>
        <item>Blade + Traemate (Apollo only) - Black</item>
        <item>Blade + Tabmate (Apollo only) - Silver</item>
        <item>Blade + Tabmate (Apollo only) - White</item>
        <item>Blade + Tabmate (Apollo only) - Black</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="title_extrusion_list">Extrusions (click item for details)</string>
    <string name="title_extrusion_detail">Extrusion Detail</string>

    <string name="warranty_text">"MODTEC WARRANTY &#xa;
‘Integ’ brand products are designed and built with reliability in mind to ensure that you have many satisfying years of dependable performance.&#xa;
Modtec provides a FIVE YEAR WARRANTY on all Integ products, against defects in materials and/or faulty workmanship. The warranty is effective from the date of purchase, to the original purchaser named above. The warranty period for all electrical parts is 12 months.&#xa;
This warranty does not cover claims for incidental or consequential damage, loss, injury, or expense due to normal wear and tear, improper use or neglect. This warranty will be considered void if it is found that the product has not been used in accordance with the manufacturers specifications or has been subjected to unauthorised alterations, abuse or damage.&#xa;
The product is designed to be fastened to a stable structure. There should be no movement or vibration in the mounting structure (wall/floor/desktop). This warranty will be considered void if the product has been installed on an unstable structure.&#xa;
If you experience any problem with an Integ product, please contact Modtec with a description of the difficulty you are experiencing. Customer satisfaction is important to us. Modtec will endeavour to help resolve your difficulty. While any difficulty with our product is very rare, it is important feedback for us and an opportunity for improvement.&#xa;
Should the Modtec investigation reveal a warranty issue, Modtec agrees to repair, replace or upgrade the product. Should the Modtec investigation reveal the issue is not a warranty issue, Modtec will report its findings and recommendations to the purchaser without charge."</string>

    <string name="refund_text">"MODTEC REFUND POLICY&#xa;
Returns&#xa;
Our policy lasts 30 days. If 30 days have gone by since your purchase, unfortunately we can’t offer you a refund or exchange.
To be eligible for a return, your item must be unused and in the same condition that you received it. It must also be in the original packaging.
To complete your return, we require a receipt or proof of purchase.&#xa;
Refunds (if applicable)&#xa;
Once your return is received and inspected, we will send you an email to notify you that we have received your returned item. We will also notify you of the approval or rejection of your refund.
If you are approved, then your refund will be processed, and a credit will automatically be applied to your credit card or original method of payment, within a certain amount of days.&#xa;
Late or missing refunds (if applicable)&#xa;
If you haven’t received a refund yet, first check your bank account again.
Then contact your credit card company, it may take some time before your refund is officially posted.
Next contact your bank. There is often some processing time before a refund is posted.
If you’ve done all of this and you still have not received your refund yet, please contact us at orders@integinternational.com&#xa;
Sale items (if applicable)&#xa;
Only regular priced items may be refunded, unfortunately sale items cannot be refunded.&#xa;
Exchanges (if applicable)&#xa;
We only replace items if they are defective or damaged. If you need to exchange it for the same item, send us an email at orders@integinternational.com and send your item to: 18 - 20 Curley Ave, Silverdale, Auckland NZ 0932.&#xa;
Shipping&#xa;
To return your product, you should mail your product to:&#xa;
18 - 20 Curley Ave, Silverdale, Auckland NZ 0932.&#xa;
You will be responsible for paying for your own shipping costs for returning your item. Shipping costs are non-refundable. If you receive a refund, the cost of return shipping will be deducted from your refund.
Depending on where you live, the time it may take for your exchanged product to reach you, may vary.
If you are shipping an item over $75, you should consider using a trackable shipping service or purchasing shipping insurance. We don’t guarantee that we will receive your returned item.
 "</string>

       <string name="pricelistquery">Type in your password to access your price lists</string>
    <string name="importance_title">What is most important out of Design, Quality, Service, Delivery and Price?</string>

</resources>
